http://www.fireball-international.com/privacy-policy/

Home
The BoatHistoryRulesAmateur buildersTuning & TrainingInteresting StoriesThe ClassStrategic PlanConstitutionNewsEventsUpcoming EventsEvents ArchiveWorlds2022 Worlds Australia2021 no event2020 Worlds Ireland2019 Worlds Canada2018 Worlds France2016 Worlds South Africa2015 Worlds Wales2014 Worlds Thailand2013 Worlds Slovenia2012 Worlds Australia2011 Worlds
Ireland2010 Worlds Barbados1980 Worlds Durban RSAResultsWorld ChampionshipsAustralian ChampionshipsEuropean ChampionshipsNorth American ChampionshipsGrand NationalGalleriesFor SaleSuppliersLinksAdminExecutive DocumentsCouncil decisionsFinancialsMarketing & PromotionWorlds Venue CriteriaMajor Event Organisation
Privacy Policy
Fireball International has created this privacy statement in
order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following
discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for
this Web site.
Information is Automatically Logged
This site uses a visitor statistics package that logs the
following information on each page access: userid, user_agent, IP,
host, browser type, computing platform, date and time, page viewed,
referer, request type, and query_string. We use this information to
help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web
site, and to help identify you. This information is also gathered
because we like to see who is visiting. This information is not and
will never be divulged to a third party.
Cookies
This site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your
interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it
each time you visit our site, and for other purposes.
Registration Forms
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact
information (i.e. email address). Contact information from the
registration forms is used to validate the user's account. This
enables the site administrators to provide moderation for the
various public features of this site, and to get in touch with the
user when necessary. This information is not and will never be
divulged to a third party. We use this data to tailor our visitor's
experience at our site showing them content that we think they
might be interested in, and displaying the content according to
their preferences.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Fireball International
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such
Web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes message boards available to its users. Please
remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas
becomes public information and you should exercise caution when
deciding to disclose your personal information. While we do our
best to ensure only appropriate information is posted, we cannot
and do not assume responsibility for our user's postings. All
postings are property of their respective author. Improper language
is automatically censored by the system. All submissions are
subject to our editorial control. Where appropriate, editorial
changes will be indicated.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss,
misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Data Quality/Access
This site gives users control over their user experience and
content that they may have provided. Users can freely modify or
delete any content they post. Users have the ability to customize
various aspects of the look and feel of the site.
Limitation of Liability
Fireball International is not liable for any damages caused by
any of the site content, whether directly provided by Fireball
International or its employees or not.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the
practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you
can contact the
webmaster.
Fireball International on Facebook >
Contacts     Terms Of Use     Privacy Policy
International Links
Copyright 2020
